(Sheldon:)I also have the other kind
of will,
(Sheldon:)and in it I will my Wil
back to Wil.
(Leonard:)Will Wil want it?
(Wil:)Wil won't.
(Penny:)What's that ring box?
(Sheldon:)Oh. That is
(Sheldon:)an engagement ring
(Sheldon:)that I was going to give
my girlfriend Amy.
What?!
(Leonard:)You bought her a ring?
No, no, no. This has been
in my family
(Sheldon:)for generations.
Except for a short time
(Sheldon:)when Comanches cut off my
great-great-great-grandmother's
(Sheldon:)finger and stole it.
(Wil:)Sheldon, that's awful.
No.
(Sheldon:)The Texas Rangers tracked them
down to their village
(Sheldon:)and slaughtered
every last one of them, so...
(Sheldon:)it was a happy ending.
(Sheldon:)Well, for my nine-fingered Nana.
(Penny:)Okay, back to the ring.
Does Amy even know about this?
(Sheldon:)No. She broke up with me before
I could broach the subject.
(Leonard:)Oh, man, I'm sorry...
that must have been devastating for you.
(Sheldon:)No, not at all.
No, I'm fine.
(Sheldon:)You know, Amy had reservations
about our relationship,
(Sheldon:)so all worked out
for the best.
PENNY: I know. It just...
SHELDON: I said I'm fine!